Goddamn little...
Mom?
Kaio!
You little shit, where the hell have you been?
I'll shoot!
I should have known.
This was all you're doing, wasn't it?
Who the hell do you think you are hiding my kid from me?
I damn near lost my mind worrying.
I'm gonna sue the shit out of you for this!
She's been gone three days.
In all that time, did you even bother looking for her?
Wait, what?
Are you...
So now I'm the bad guy?
You goddamn bitch!
I'll kill you!
Kaio!
Let go of me!
You didn't worry about her.
The only person you were worrying about was yourself.
What?
Do you know what?
I'm the bad guy.
Love to be best!
作詞・作曲・編曲 初音ミク
作曲・編曲 初音ミク
Dammit, Kyle! They're calling me right now!
You hear me?
Talking to you, you little retard!
Miss Hinazuki, that's enough.
Do you think it's fun for her seeing you act like this?
That's your fault!
You called me a piece of shit mom in front of my daughter!
Who the hell do you think you are, taking people's kids away?
Shut up!
You're the one that beats her and throws her in sheds.
She's been gone three days and you've done jack shit!
I'm not going to stand here and get lectured by you, you brat.
You don't know what being a pair is like!
Get out of here, you!
Ms. Inazuki!
We're with the Department of Child Protective Services.
Huh?
We'd like to speak to you about your daughter.
Now we can do this the easy way or the hard way.
It's up to you.
Goddamn the both of you.
You tricked me.
Don't blame Ms. Fuji-numa.
She's here because we asked her.
You've been avoiding us, so we really didn't have any other choice.
I what?
I wasn't avoiding you!
Regardless, we're here now.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to have to drag you into this.
No, you don't have to be.
There were a couple things I wanted to say to her myself.
I'm glad you gave me the opportunity to.
Last I checked, kidnapping someone's kid was still illegal.
You gonna call the cops or what?
No.
We're not calling anyone until we've had a chance to speak to you about your daughter's welfare.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Now that she's back home with me, she'll be fine.
Based on the facts at hand, I'm afraid we'll have to take custody of her.
What?
I'm her mother, you asshole!
Like the boy said, she was gone for three days and you didn't look for her.
What, are you denying that?
That son of a...
He's the one who took her!
What are you people nuts?
I'm not the criminal here!
Miss Inazuki, please.
Let's talk calmly about this.
Okay.
Let's all go talk to the cops.
What?
You heard me.
They can settle this.
Come on, Kaio.
Wait, hold on.
Calm down.
Miss Inazuki.
You're not helping your daughter.
Where are you going?
God damn it.
Stop dragging your feet.
Kaio, move it, you little...
Akimi!
Akimi?
Mom?
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault we haven't spoken since I made you leave that man.
And ever since, I've been worrying about you and Kaio.
I know what it's like trying to raise a kid all by yourself.
All the sacrifices you have to make.
It must have been tough for you.
And lonely, too.
I should have taken you both in and helped you.
You had to deal with so much.
I should have been there for you.
Please don't blame her.
This is my fault.
If I was around, this wouldn't have happened.
Mom.
I wasn't buying it.
If anything, she felt sorry for herself.
Kaio wasn't buying any of it, either.
She wouldn't even look at her mom.
I don't blame her.
Akimi?
Don't you worry about Kaio now.
I promise you, I'll take good care of her.
I can't imagine what you're going through.
My child's the most precious thing I have.
He's my everything, and I know Kaio is yours.
Thanks, Mr. Yashiro.
No.
The reason we're all here is because of you, Satoru.
After everything you've done, and all the courage you've shown,
this couldn't have ended any better.
Thanks to you, she's alive.
I can barely remember my dad.
I wonder if he was anything like Mr. Yashiro.
Thank you, Satoru.
You got me out of this nightmare.
Kaio, ready?
The Town Without Me, by Kaio Hinazuki.
When I get bigger, big enough to go somewhere by myself,
I want to go someplace far away from here.
I want to go to an island.
An island without any people.
An island that doesn't have any pain or sadness on it, either.
When I feel like I want to climb a tree, I can climb it.
I'll go for a swim if I want to, and sleep when I want to.
And when I think about the town without me,
I feel relief more than anything.
All I want is to go far away.
I did it.
I saved Kaio.
I changed things so she could have a future.
Now she has a chance to grow up to be whatever she wants to be.
She's on her way.
And I have a feeling she's going to be just fine.
Is he okay?
He's been like this ever since Kaio left.
He's in hibernation mode.
Being a superhero takes a lot out of a guy.
Hey, Satoru.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Great.
I don't know, dude.
You don't look it.
Jeez, can you blame him?
I mean, his girlfriend moved to another town.
Well, the important thing is, she's safe now.
Satoru, can I see you for a sec?
I have some news.
Kaio's grandmother has full custody of her now.
And as for Kaio's mother,
the authorities aren't going to let her see her for a while.
Thank you, Mr. Yashiro.
Well, you deserve to know.
It's not about that.
You said it couldn't have ended any better
after what I did and the courage I showed.
I just wanted to let you know that meant a lot to me.
Well, actually,
I wanted to say you deserve to be rewarded for your courage,
but that would have sounded awful.
Not that you shouldn't be rewarded,
because if anyone deserves to be, it's you.
I bet seeing Kaio's smile was your reward, wasn't it?
Your smile was mine.
Oh, by the way,
where was Kaio staying?
At your house?
No, not there.
We hit her.
Seriously?
Yep.
We set her up in this old bus
Izumi Elementary's hockey club used to use.
Huh.
I guess if you want to kidnap someone,
that's a perfect place to take him, huh?
I guess.
If he only knew.
Even though Kaio's safe now,
Aya, Nakanishi, and Hiromi are still in danger.
I have to figure out a way to make sure
neither of them are left alone.
Like how I did with Kaio.
Hiromi's my friend, and I'm with him all the time.
But Aya goes to a different school,
and I don't know her.
So how do I approach her?
I heard she sometimes hangs out with Yuki.
So maybe he's my in.
I don't know her.
She doesn't know me.
This is gonna be tough.
Wait, how do you make friends with someone you don't know?
Easy.
Be honest and say something like,
Hey you, let's be friends.
That's never gonna work.
You're thinking that's never gonna work,
but it might.
Psychic witch.
I can't believe you're already looking for another girlfriend.
How do you know him?
I didn't, but I do now.
You're right.
This person's a girl.
But I just wanna be her friend.
Well, if that's what you want,
then what's the harm in asking?
To get what you want in life,
you have to think positively.
You never know till you try.
I have to go somewhere really quick.
Is it cool if I meet you guys at the Children's Center?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, see you guys in a little bit.
Later.
See ya!
Looks like her class gets out at 6.30.
I can walk Hiromi home and be back here in time.
I have to get familiar with Aya's daily routine.
Aya pretty much kept to a straightforward schedule.
If someone wanted to kidnap her,
the best time would be right now,
after she got out of cram school.
Satoru!
I need your muscles.
Come on, shake a leg.
Why'd she have to show up now?
I'm trying to find out where Aya lives.
Why the heck'd you buy all this stuff?
Couldn't help it.
It was cheap.
It's heavy.
God, stop complaining.
It'll only make it heavier.
It'd be as heavy either way.
You're a lifesaver, sir.
Mom sort of went nuts at the store.
I did not go nuts.
So, Mr. Yoshiro,
how come you're not married?
That came out of nowhere.
It's like this.
Getting married depends on finding the right partner.
It depends on timing,
and whether they want to marry you,
and, well, other things.
Me?
I already failed horribly at it once,
so I guess I'm just being extra cautious.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to...
It's okay.
It's all in the past now.
I was wondering if you could give me some advice.
How to approach a girl you don't know, huh?
Yeah.
I know a couple things about her, but that's it.
Let's see.
How would I go about doing that?
I guess I'd get her to drop her guard first.
That way I won't freak her out.
How do I do that?
Easy.
When you're around her, be yourself.
That's all.
Whatever you're into,
be it sports or cooking,
your interests make you interesting.
Your enthusiasm will make her curious,
and then she'll drop her guard.
Whoa.
I wish it were that impressive.
No, I'm bad at expressing my feelings directly,
so I've gotten good at relying on logic.
What's this doing here?
No.
No, don't touch it!
I didn't mean to...
What the...
Well, my secret's out.
Candy?
There's no sense in hiding the truth anymore.
Don't just sit there.
Help me eat the evidence.
I quit smoking three years ago,
and candy's the only thing that helps stop the cravings.
I find someplace private,
jam a couple of these in my mouth,
and I'm good.
What a weirdo.
Thank you.
Can I bum one of those off you?
Sure.
I'm going over to the children's center to do my homework.
Okay.
Um, if you wait a sec, I'll go with you.
Are you gonna be Hiromi's bodyguard now that Kaio's gone?
It's not like that.
Satoru, can I talk to you for a sec?
Uh-huh.
Sorry.
I'll catch up in a few, okay?
Mm-hmm.
I have no idea what's going on with you lately.
You made it your mission to save Kaio, and you did,
so what's bothering you?
You always look so intense,
like you're still trying to fix whatever it is that needs fixing.
If something's bugging you,
I wish you'd just tell me about it.
I can't really explain what it is.
I'm still trying to figure it out.
Then, let me help you figure it out.
I'd like the chance to be a hero, too.
Whatever you're up to, I'd like to come along.
Check it out.
What do you think of these footprints?
A grown-up was here.
They came and left.
Yeah, but no tread.
It's like he wrapped his shoes in something.
Why?
They'd be super slippy.
Maybe to hide the tread pattern.
Look, the backpack's gone.
Crap.
Box with the stove, too.
Quite a few boxes are missing.
Andy tore some open.
He didn't want to leave any evidence behind.
Satoru, where are you going with this?
You guys remember what Kaio told us?
That night she was here alone and she heard someone come in?
Yeah.
He left a backpack full of creepy junk.
So what?
I think that guy, whoever he is,
is a serial killer who targets kids.
Wait, a serial killer?
You're joking.
No, I'm not.
I know it's hard to believe, but that's what I think.
Okay, but like, why?
I wish I could explain it to you guys, but I can't.
When I saw the stuff from the backpack and the stove and charcoal,
I thought maybe the killer was using this as their home base.
I know, guys.
Everything I just said to you sounds totally crazy.
But even so, I think I'm right.
As for Kaio, the truth is,
it wasn't just because her mom beat her that I didn't want to leave her alone.
I was also protecting her from the killer.
Geez, it's so out there,
it's like the plot of some detective story.
But the real issue here
isn't whether we believe in your theory or not.
It's about whether we believe in you or not.
You don't have to walk me all the way home.
I can take care of myself, you know?
I had to swing by here for something else anyway.
Okay.
Satoru?
What?
I believe what you told us before.
And I'll do whatever I can to help out.
You can totally count on me.
You're the best.
See ya!
Night, Hiromi!
See you later!
I have to be honest here, Satoru.
After hearing your story,
I'm about 99% sure it's nonsense.
But still,
there's a 1% chance everything you said's true.
Well, from your point of view,
I get how you think I'm making it up
and just playing detective and...
You should keep playing detective.
I don't know what that stuff we found here was for,
but you seem to really believe something's up,
and that makes me think that you might be onto something.
Mm-hmm.
Besides, you trusted us enough to tell us about it.
If you believe in us that much,
we believe in you.
If someone believes in you,
you're not alone.
And if I was in your situation,
I'd want someone to believe me.
Thank you, Kenya.
You too, Hiromi.
You don't get it.
I could have saved her.
18 years ago,
I was crying when I said that to my mom.
I don't want to feel that kind of guilt again.
I'm the only one who can stop this.
The only one who can save them.
Remember to get your parents' signature.
Don't forget now.
I need you guys to come with me,
but just us, okay?
Hey, Satoru,
today's a good day to go to the hideout.
Actually,
we have to take care of something.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, sorry.
That's cool.
See ya.
I wonder what the heck those dudes are up to.
They're acting weird.
Wanna follow them?
Mm-hmm.
Come on!
Right behind ya!
I wonder what the heck those dudes are up to.
don't worry.
Oh, Jesus!
Thank you.